you have no meat no meat no sausage
нету у тебя мяса ни мяса ни колбасы нету
nothing nothing
ничего
please here is the
пожалуйста вот это
sausage where I can't see wait you are
колбаса где я не вижу подожди это ты
far away here is the
далеко Вот это
sausage so it's
колбаса
not clear of course it
так непонятно конечно это не Заводская
wasn't some kind of factory sausage like that And what is this What is
колбаса была какая-то так А это что А
in the yellow bowl
что в жёлтой миске
Oh hello great You  from Russia I see it that way
О привет здорово Ты из России я так вижу
Yes, I understand I'm from Ukraine the city of Khmelnitsky
Да понял я из Украины город Хмельницкий
And where do you live in Russia Astrakhan Oh,
А ты где живёшь в России Астрахань О
that's cool My dad is from
прикольно У меня батя из
Astrakhan
Астрахани
yes he's from Astrakhan yes he Under the Soviet Union he
да астраханец да он При Советском Союзе
went to study in Kharkov and
типа поехал учиться в Харьков и тут
stayed here Since
остался С какого
when do I even know anything
рана я вообще знаю ниг
back in  Astrakhan then the Soviet Union
назад в Астрахань потом Советский Союз
collapsed and that's
распался и
it Well that's how it happens And yes that's how
всё Ну это так бывает А да это тут такое
life is here I understood how things are with you everything is
жизнь такая понял как как там у тебя что
calm everything is great with me What do you
спокойно всё у меня всё замечательно Кем
work as a
работаешь
welder How much does a welder
сварщиков Сколько сейчас сварщик
get now Well at the moment I work in the
получает Ну в данный момент я работаю в
city of
городе
Kaliningrad I'm on
Калининграде Я в
a business trip  how much does a welder
командировке сколько там сварщик
get now?
получает сейчас
Well,
Ну
750 an hour, and how much do you get per month?
750 в час а в месяц сколько получается у
Well, 200, like that, 200 at a time, 2000 dollars
Ну 200 вот так вот по 200 2000 долларов
per month  Yes, I don't know in dollars I don't know
в месяц Да я не знаю в долларах не знаю
I understand I think it's
понял Я считаю
normal It's cool Now the hedgehog is singing
нормальным Прикольно Сейчас Еж поть
for the
за с
war is going on Has it become better to live or worse in
идт война лучше жить стало или хуже в
Russia in
России в
Russia Nothing has changed at all
России Да вообще ничего не поменялось
Everything is as it was and is, that is, as it was
Всё как было так и есть то есть как было
and
так и
is, why are you insulting  me not you I
есть зачем ты Оскорбляешь меня не тебя я
situation Well damn it was all Nothing you
ситуацию Ну блин было всё Ничего ты
said nothing has changed No well it was
сказал ничего не изменилось Не ну было
normal that's how it is Normal Normal
нормально так и есть Нормально Нормально
And what's normal there
А что там нормально
How much does your car cost now there
Сколько сейчас тачка у вас стоит там
Lada for example
Лада например
In short I'm going to buy a car now in
Короче я сейчас собираюсь покупать тачку
short M 300 Lagrand how much does it cost
короче м 300 лагран стоит сколько стоит
million 300 133.000 dollars is the cost of Lada
лям 300 133.000 долларов стоит Лада
Granta
Гранта
not for 13000 dollars in Europe you can
не за 13000 долларов в Европе можно
buy a normal Tola but
нормальную толу купить а
don't buy it who is not giving it to you And you
не покупайте что кто же вам не даёт А вы
in A in Kaliningrad there
в А в Калининграде там на ладах грантах
they drive Lada Grants or European cars here
ездит или на европейских тачках здесь
everyone mostly drives European
все в основном ездят на европейских
cars Hmm  I wonder why in
тачках Хм интересно А почему в
Kaliningrad everyone drives European
Калининграде все ездят на европейских
cars and no one wants to buy a Lada
тачках А никто не хочет купить себе Ладу
Granta Why does no one want to  buy Lada
Гранту Почему никто не хочет купить Лада
Granta they drive Lada Grants And why do
Гранту ездиют и на Лада грантах А почему
they mainly drive European cars
ездиют в основном на европейских тачках
Yes, because here is such a region,
Да потому что здесь район такой
as they say, a European
получается как говорится европейская
country Well, Kaliningrad This is Europe, so this is the
страна Ну Калининград Это Европа так это
former Yunes Berg, right
бывший юнес Берг правильно
German Here it is even allowed to
немецкий Здесь даже разрешено короче
buy
покупать
cars, in short, register them here, but in Russia  you
машины оформлять здесь их но в России ты
won't be able to drive them
на них ездить не сможешь
because, well, in short, they are allowed
потому что ну короче им разрешено здесь
here in Kaliningrad,
здесь в Калининграде
they are allowed, you know, to buy
разрешено так понимаешь покупать Тачки
such European cars, but in Russia you
такие европейские но в России ты на них
won't be able to drive them. And why is that?
ездить не сможешь А почему так
Kaliningrad is also Russia. It's Russia.
Калининград - это ж тоже Россия это
Yes, it's Russia. Why do you say that?  in
Да это Россия Почему так ты говоришь в
Kaliningrad you can but in Russia you can't
Калининграде можно а в России не сможешь
drive Why is that because you'll have to
ездить Почему так ну потому что надо
slow them down and then back and forth But
будет их растормозить и там туда-сюда А
here it's easier for them
здесь у них и с этим проще
and what's the problem with moving a car from
а в чём проблема перевести тачку из
Kaliningrad to Moscow or
Калининграда там в Москву или в
Astrakhan No, there are no problems here
Астрахань Нет проблем тут нет никаких
just so that you come to Russia
просто чтобы тебе приехать в Россию
specifically Kaliningrad region is
именно Калининградская область Находится
in such a position that as they say that
в таком положение что как говорится что
Kaliningrad region has a city
у Калининградской области город
Kaliningrad they can buy
Калининград они могут покупать
European cars without a bazaar and drive
европейские машины без базара и ездить
them only
них на них только
but you will come to Russia you
но приехать приедешь Ты в Россию тебе
will have to
придется её
unbrakes it for not unbraking
растормаживается на не расторможенность
now I have earned
сейчас вот заработал
money and I am going to go home in March
денег и собираюсь ехать домой в марте
and I will go in short and buy myself a car
месяце и поеду короче и куплю себе тачку
well and how does it work out Well  how much does
хорошо а как получается Ну сколько стоит
this car brake release cost
вот это растормаживание
Damn I don't know
машины Блин я не знаю
Well why is it called
Ну а почему оно называется
brake release Yeah I don't know I'm
растормаживается Да не знаю я что-то у
asking me something I'm asking what about
меня спрашиваю я что те
brake release oh well have you ever seen
расторможенность а ну ты когда-то видел
brake release
расторможенность
you drive on it
на ней гоняешь
no problems in short it costs
никаких проблем нет короче это стоит
thirty Well what  and vice versa, to
тридцатка Ну что а наоборот чтобы с
drive it from Kaliningrad to Astrakhan, how much does it
Калининграда загнать в Астрахань сколько
cost to unfreeze
стоит чтобы растормозить
it? I don't know, I don't know these bastards, I
её Я не знаю не знаю этих су не
understand. I understand. It's
знаем понял
interesting, yes. Listen, how does it
Понял интересно да Слушай а как
work out? For example, Well,
получается Например Ну что вс-таки
Kaliningraders don't want to buy
калининградцы не хотят покупать
Russian cars like Lada Granta.
российские машины типа Лады Гранты
Why don't they want to? Well, they  basically They are
Почему не хотят Ну они же в основном Они
mainly for disinhibition
же в основном на расторможенность
Listen, for example, how much does a
Слушай а вот например Сколько стоит
European car cost, which is also what kind of
европейская тачка которая тоже вот какую
European car can you buy for  million 300
европейскую тачку можно за лям 300
buy a European car Yes for 133,000
купить европейскую тачку Да за 133.000
dollars
долларов
Yes what kind can you buy Well
Да какие можно купить Ну бэушную
used for example well used As they say with
например ну бэушную Как говорится с
mileage you won't buy a new one for Lem
пробегом новую ты не купишь за Лем
300 new you won't buy for Len 300 but with
300 новый ты не купишь за Лен 300 но с
mileage
пробегом
what kind yes Well look it seems to me that in
каких да Ну смотри мне кажется что в
Europe for a million  300 Yes, for 13,000 dollars you
Европе за лям 300 Да за 13000 долларов
can buy normal cars, brand new,
можно нормальных тачек купить новеньких
without
без
mileage, I don’t know, I don’t know, I don’t know,
пробега не знаю не знаю не знаю я не это
I’m
как я
not such a professional in this crap, but
не не такой профессионал в этой фигне но
I’ll tell you that you
я тебе скажу что
can buy an Audi BHU here for Len 300 And
Audi бху можно здесь купить за Лен 300 А
how is it that in Russia  Russian
как так получается что в России русские
cars are more expensive and worse
машины дороже и хуже
How is it that Repeat the question
Как так получается что Повтори вопрос
how is it that in Russia cars are
как так получается что в России машины
worse and more
хуже и
expensive worse and more expensive
дороже хуже и дороже
Yes more expensive than what more expensive than European and
Да дороже чего дороже чем европейские и
worse than
хуже чем
European they are not worse than European
европейские они не хуже чем европейские
I'll tell you so good come on come on
я тебе скажу так хорошо давай ска Давай
tell me what Lada  Granta is better than
скажи чем Лада Гранта лучше например
Volvo, for example. Don't compare Volvo and Lada
Volvo не Ты не сравнивай Volvo и Лада
Granta. Volvo is a
Гранта Volvo - это
professional. Okay, let's do what we can.
профессионал Хорошо давай с чем можно с
what European car can we compare
каким европейской машиной мы сравним
Lada Granta with? Yes, I don't know which one I
Ладу Гранту Да я не знаю с какой я даже
can't even compare it with. Let's compare it with Skoda. Let's
не могу сравнивать Давай со шкодой наме
compare it with Skoda. How is Vlada Granta better? Yes, it's
со шкодой сравним чем Влада Гранта лучше
not better at all. It's so good that
шды Да ничем не лучше так хорошо чем
Lada Granta is better. It's the
Лада Гранта лучше
same.
одинаково
Yes, and what is the same between Vlada Granta and
да а что одинаково Влади Гранта и
Renault? Yes.  everything is the same it turns out to be
Renault Да всё одинаково она получается
Lada Gran it is written off from
Лада Гран она и списана с
Renault once again Agra is written off from Renault
Renault ещё раз Агра списана с Renault
yes in
да по
form and in essence and
форме и по сути и
in appearance and the engine is there from but
по внешности и двигатель там от но
No no no the engine is not
Нет нет нет двигатель там не стоит отно
there relatively But the engine
Но двигатель там
is there like that you take and insult Well
стоит вот так берёшь и оскорбляешь Ну
Vlady  Gran is really
Влады Гран реально
an engine
двигатель
that Well, let
что Ну пускай для тебя
it be for you Well, I'll tell you that it's 200,000 oet
будет Ну я тебе скажу что он 200000 оет
right
пр
vu
вю
problems after 200,000 from Lada Granta
проблем через 200.000 от Лады Гранты
there's a basin left Well,
остаётся тазик Да ну
if you drove a Lada Granta Thank God
если ты ездил на лади Гранте Слава богу
no Well, you see God forbid you drive a Lada Granta
нет Ну вот видишь Упаси на Ладе Гранте
And I'll buy myself one  Lada
кататься А я куплю себе Ладу
Granta Why exactly Why exactly
Гранту А почему именно А почему именно
Lada Gran I said and I'll buy myself  Lada
Ладу Гран говорил и куплю себе Ладу
Granta, I'm answering. I understand. Why
Гранту вот отвечаю я Поня А почему
exactly Lada Granta? Why? Because
именно Ладу Гранту Почему Потому что
it's a good car. What's good about it? Well, it's
хорошая машина чем Она хороша Ну она
good in everything. What's good in
всем хороша Чем
everything? Well, tell me specifically. Does it have a
всем Ну конкретно скажи у неё Двигатель
good engine here or
хороший там или
there? At least it has everything. It
там А бска хоть есть у неё всё у неё
has airbags, yes, and
есть подушки безопасности есть да
heating.  seats in short
подогрев сидений короче
heated glass these
подогрев стёкл вот этих
mirrors everything is there
зеркалов всё есть
Cool and noise insulation is
Прикольно да шумка
complete Yes cool good and
полностью Да прикольно хорошо а телефон
what kind of phone will you buy there Russian I
какой ты там купишь русский Я так
understand well you buy a Russian car Lada Gran
понимаю ну машину русскую Ладу Гран
and you buy a Russian phone What kind is
купишь а телефон русский покупаешь Какой
it I don't know why do you need to
это я не знаю ну зачем тебе Тода
know Toda brand What kind of
знать марка Какая
phone in  I mean, show me your phone
телефона в смысле Ты покажи свой телефон
So what is yours, just Russian or not
Так какая у тебя просто русская или не
Russian, tell me Yes, of course, Russian, a Russian
русская скажи Да конечно русская русский
phone is absolutely like Russian, Samsung
телефон абсолютно как русский Samsung
Lenovo, what is it called? What Russian
Lenovo как он называется Какая русская
company is Russian called a phone, the company that
фирма Русский называется телефо фирма
makes the phone is called
производитель фо называется телефон
Russian, yes, background, Well, show me where the
русский да фон А ну покажи где там
emblem logo is  Show me this
эмблема логотип Покажи этого
background from behind,
фона сзади
turn it around, it's not there, there's no background, it
разверни не там не фон там английское
says Chinese in English, well,
пишет Китая ну
look, look carefully, there's no background, there's no
посмотри смотри хорошенько фон нет
label, show me the label, I
этикетку Покажи мне этикетку я этикетку
'll read the label, there's a label on it, but  this is not a
прочитаю там на этикетке но это не
Russian phone It says look
русский телефон Там написано посмотри
where it was made look this is a Russian
где где произведено посмотри это русский
phone not Russian Look No yes background I'm
телефон не русский Посмотри Нет да фон я
telling you Tanya Russian phone You don't have a
тебе говорю Тани русский телефон Нет у
Russian phone haha ​​you see
тебя телефона русского хаха видишь С
Where did you get that from So you don't have a Russian
чего ты взял Так у тебя не русский
phone you have a NATO phone What
телефон у тебя натовский телефон Какой
NATO phone  NATO countries
натовский телефон страны НАТО
And also tell me that I also have
Да ещё Скажи что у меня и наушники тоже
NATO headphones NATO headphones
натовские наушники натовские
yes NATO yes
да натовские да
let the only Russian here is you yourself
пускай из русского только ты сам
well and the Armed Forces and thank
тут ну и ВС и слава
God
Богу
for How do you think why Russia
при Как ты считаешь почему вот Россия
has oil gas gold diamonds the Armed Forces the
имеет нефть газ золото алмазы ВС таблицу
periodic table but lives poorer than Europe  And
Менделеева а живут беднее чем Европа А
who told you that we live poorer than
кто тебе сказал что мы живём беднее Чем
Europe Well, even in Kaliningrad you can see Yes,
Европа Ну даже в Калининграде видно Да
Europe is nearby and you
рядом Европа и
can see that we live poorer than Europe What are you
видно мы живём беднее Чем Европа Ты что
kidding, tell me well, do you live like the rich people of
прикалываешься хорошо расскажи вы живёте
Europe Yes, I just laugh at
Европы Да мне смешно просто
what you are saying, my friend How can we
ты что говоришь дружище Как мы можем
if we are the richest country  in the world and
если мы самая богатая страна в мире и
we live worse than
живём хуже чем
Europe explain how it happens that you
Европа объясни как так получается что вы
live the same way that you
живёте же
carry some kind of we live better than
чем какую-то несёшь мы живём лучше
everyone else we live better than everyone else
всех мы живём лучше всех
That's good  how much is your salary and
Вот хорошо сколько зарплата у вас И
how much is it in Europe yes I already
сколько в Европе да я же тебе уже
told you about my salary so in Europe there are
говорил про сво зарплату так в Европе
more salaries in Europe there are
больше в Европе зарплаты
more salaries I put on this
больше я ложил на эту
Europe No well honestly if I have enough
Европу Не ну вот честно если мне хватает
money that's where I live now in Russia I
денег вот где я живу сейчас в России Мне
have enough money not yours  Europe is
хватает бабло не твоя Европа
super, look up to it, to this Europe. Yes,
супер равняться на неё на эту Европу Да
go ahead, you live there in your Europe, you have
идт живёте вы там в своей Европе у вас
everything there, and we have everything here too. Yes, but it's better in
всё и у нас тоже здесь всё Да но в
Europe. Yes,
Европе
why is it
лучше Да почему
better? Look, because Russians live in
лучше смотри потому что россияне живут в
poverty, drive poor cars, and eat
нищете ездят на нищих машинах Да едят
poor products. Yes,  Who told you that
нищие продукты Да Кто тебе такое сказал
Well,
Ну вот
you are a European, you will never in your life sit on a car, you will
ты европеец никогда в жизни не сядет на
never buy a Lada Granta, never in your
не купит себе Ладу Гранту никогда в
life
жизни
Why? Because this car is just awful,
Почему Потому что эта машина просто ужас
explain well why people in Russia are richer than in
хорошо объясни чем в России богаче чем в
Europe
Европе
Yes,
люди Да всем
we are simply richer in our human souls
просто душой человеческой душой мы
than the Europeans  we just
богаче чем чем европейцы просто душой мы
understand each other with our souls, we respect each other, and we love each other,
друг друга понимаем уважаем И любим
you know, I understand, well, look at your
понимаешь понял ну смотри за свою
salary, how many phones and
зарплату Сколько сможет там телефонов и
cars can Europeans buy, how many can a Russian
машин купить европейцы сколько россиянин
buy? I mean, what should I buy for one salary? How many cars should I buy, let's do it this way, how
Сколько я должен машин купить давай так
many?  you need a salary to buy a
сколько тебе нужно зарплат чтобы купить
car Well, damn, I don't
машину Ну блин я не
know Well, how much if you count like this
знаю Ну сколько если вот так вот считать
if I don't spend anything, just
если я ничего не трачу прям вот чисто
pay my salary for the car,
зарплату отдаю за машину
right Yes Well, look, 200,000 I
правильно Да Ну вот смотри 200.000 Я
get, that means In 5 months I'll buy
получаю это значит За 5 месяцев я куплю
myself a car for not 5  months A for
себе машину не за 5 месяцев А за
Sem Well let it be for seven for seven yes that is
Сем Ну пускай за семь за семь да то есть
if you don't eat anything for 7 months
если ты 7 месяцев не будешь ничего жрать
work on a shift You will only be able to
работать на вахте Ты только сможешь
buy a Lada Granta a European will be able to
купить Ладу Гранту европеец сможет
buy a car for himself in 3 months Good luck
купить за 3 месяца Машину себе да Удачи
Well let it be a handsome man simply Why are
Ну пускай красавчик просто Почему
Europeans richer than Russians if he  can
европейцы богаче русские если он может
buy a car for himself in 7 months Yes I
купить за 7 месяцев себе машину Да я его
just greet him Well handsome yes So
только Приветствую Ну красав да Так
why how is it that they are
почему как так получается что они
richer who are Europeans Yes and let them
богаче кто европейцы Да и пускай они
be richer Well and I just
будут богаче Ну и на них я просто
asked them yes on nifi Well look Why is it like that
спросил да на нифи Ну смотри Почему так
Well why is it like that well because  what
Ну почему так ну потому что
Well because well okay it seems to me that
Ну потому что ну ладно мне кажется что
you are even lying about 200,000 you
ты даже обманываешь про 200.000 у тебя
don't even have normal products  eat
даже продуктов нету нормальных покушать
I don't have any
У меня нету
yes you all Russians who speak I say
да вы все русские кто говорят я говорю
Show me the products And they have a Beggar
Покажите продукты А у них Нищий проду у
they don't have any products Even some kind of sausage butter
них нету Даже колбасы какой-то масла
sour cream nothing from dairy and meat to
сметаны ничего нету из молочки и мяса
you what is a refrigerator from Prish Well show me
тебе что холодильник от приш Ну покажи
if if you have money to me Me
если если у тебя есть деньги мне Мне
it seems that you live very poorly You
кажется что ты бедно очень живёшь У тебя
can't have it Come on
не может быть давай
what do you see you don't have any
что ты во видишь нету у тебя у тебя
meat products at all Listen you're going
мясных изделий вообще нет Слышь ты пошл
Aha, that's it, no, no, no So that's how I
Ага всё нету нету нету Значит так я
understood it, you're all deceiving me about 200,000
понял вот вы все обману про 200.000
now I'll show you and then go I don't have any  you have
сейчас покажу а потом пошл нету у тебя
no meat no meat no sausage nothing nothing
мяса ни мяса ни колбасы нету ничего
please here is the sausage
пожалуйста вот это колбаса
where I don't see wait you are far away here is the
где я не вижу подожди ты далеко Вот это
sausage
колбаса
so it is not clear of course it
так непонятно конечно это не Заводская
was not some kind of factory sausage so what is this what is
колбаса была какая-то так А это что А
in the yellow
что в жёлтой
bowl what was that you had there  it's not
миске что это у тебя было там это не
sausage it's some kind of I don't know what it
колбаса это какой-то не знаю что это
was you took it with your hands it wasn't sausage
было ты её руками взял это не колбаса
it was to unblock
была растормозить
a millionaire Damn if you
миллионера Блин если вы
got infected you have to leave a comment  and
заражались обяза оставить комент и
send this funny letter to your friends on my
скинуть друзьям этот ржач пись на мий
Telegram right now axis VN
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos are not shown to people at times
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
information about streams is not shown so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational links
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
are written  right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams okrim video also interesting and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
to trim the current operational connection
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
write and
пиши а